[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", ":", "IN", ",", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "VBD", "NNS", ",", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 32, "question": "What is your reaction to this video?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 33, "answer": "We just looked at the video and we were just surprised of -- because, according to the police report, he sustained injuries, Zimmerman sustained injuries, but when we looked at the video, it was obvious that there were no visible injuries.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "VBZ", ":", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 44, "question": "How significant is this from a legal point of view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 45, "answer": "Piers, this is -- smoking gun.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "I mean, from everything that you have seen, that you've read, that you've heard, what do you believe is the most likely set of circumstances that led to your son being killed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "VBZ", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "I believe that George Zimmerman hunted my son like an animal, tried to detain my son.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "Sybrina, do you believe if your son had been white and George Zimmerman had been black, that he would have been arrested, George Zimmerman?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "I absolutely believe that my son would have been arrested.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 103, "question": "What is it, as his mother, that you would like to see happen next?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 104, "answer": "I would like George Zimmerman arrested immediately.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "And do you believe that the video that's emerged tonight should lead to that arrest on the basis that the story that's been put out here in George Zimmerman's defense, that he was being beaten so badly he feared for his life, cannot, as this video would suggest, be true?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "VBN", "VBN", "RP", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "MD", "RB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I believe that this video is the icing on the cake.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sybrina"]}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "RBR", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "IN", "WDT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 117, "question": "And I just want -- I would just ask him, why did he in fact take my son's life and how does he feel about taking my son's life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "CC", "WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 118, "answer": "And Sybrina, many believe that you are suffering perhaps even more now since losing your son by the attempt by some people to assassinate his character, to bring out all this stuff about his behavior in school and so on which portrays him in a very damaging light.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 119, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 120, "answer": "It bothers me as a mother to hear all of those negative things about my son.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 169, "question": "What did you make of what they were saying?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 170, "answer": "You know, I'm a parent.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "But it's just one of those situations where every parent in America, in the world would say, what happened?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", ",", "WDT", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "It's really important, it seems to me, that you have to allow the legal process to take its course.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Wild West"]}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 210, "question": "Doesn't give you the right to pull out a gun and shoot him in the street, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 211, "answer": "We're bringing back the Wild West.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 248, "question": "When was the first time that you realized there was racism in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 249, "answer": "I experienced it for the first time with the Commodores.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "Really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 303, "question": "You understand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 304, "answer": "I understand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "Am I moving you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "The thing about you was you had all the Commodore stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "``", "JJ", "''", "CC", "``", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 340, "question": "Would it really?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 341, "answer": "It would be \"Easy\" or \"All Night Long.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "Are you for real a sensitive, romantic, loving type of guy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", ",", "JJ", ",", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "I am a hopeless romantic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 374, "question": "How many times have you been properly in love in your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 375, "answer": "God, you would ask that question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "You remember that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I do remember.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 382, "question": "Do I have to say it out loud?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 383, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RB", "VBD", "CD", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 387, "question": "And how old was she?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 388, "answer": "And I should say there was one more.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP$", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 392, "question": "But these are your first loves?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 393, "answer": "These are the ones where you go, oh, my God.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 401, "question": "So you married two of the three people you've been properly in love with?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 402, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RB", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 405, "question": "In what sense?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 406, "answer": "Well, you think a little bit more before you say I love you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "What have you really learned about love?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "That you have to throw yourself into it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "How do you do it in your marriage?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "Well, mine's easy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "Do they get on now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Oh no, it's perfect.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "Do you sing at these little tribal meetings?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "Absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 477, "question": "Go on?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 478, "answer": "I will tell you right now, he's not in love yet.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "You mean my first love was not enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 501, "question": "Who is the biggest romantic sexual singer you've ever deployed?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 502, "answer": "Holy cow.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 505, "question": "Has to be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 506, "answer": "Has to be.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "You understand me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "I think I understand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Barry White"], "PERSON": ["Smoky Robinson"]}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 513, "question": "Ever had a Barry White night?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 514, "answer": "Barry White and Smoky Robinson.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Barry White"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 518, "question": "And candle lit rooms?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 519, "answer": "You understand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 536, "question": "You understand?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 537, "answer": "I understand.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Do you understand that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "I understand that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBD", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "You like that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "That was better than mine.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NNS", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "What does the pressure of performance become like when you're going through that deterioration?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "You are going through what we call panic, because we are perfectionists, or as I say, all artists -- we're egotistical maniacs with inferiority complexes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120328pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "CD", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJS", "VBD", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG"], "qSentId": 649, "question": "I said who sang the best line?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "WP", "NN", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 650, "answer": "The one that I loved the most was, there's a choice we're making", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]